guildomatic.com 2014-04-20

# Guildomatic : Guildomatic Privacy Policy

### Guildomatic Privacy Policy

This policy states the terms under which information about you is collected and used while accessing Guildomatic websites. By accessing Guildomatic websites, you agree to the terms and conditions set forth in this policy.

#### Personally identifying information submitted

Guildomatic does not collect any personally identifying information about users, which includes, but is not limited to, your name, address, telephone number and email address unless it is voluntarily submitted to us through our registration forms, order processing, email or any other means. 

#### Profile and cookies

We may automatically collect certain non-identifying information about users as they visit Guildomatic websites. Additionally, we may use cookies to enable us to enhance the efficiency and usefullness of Guildomatic websites. You can, optionally, disable cookies in your browser if you object to this practice. If you created a user account with profile information including, but not limited to, your email address, user name and password, this information is collected only for use internally and is not shared with any third parties. 

#### Third-party websites

Guildomatic websites may display advertising with links to websites of third-party advertisers. These websites may have privacy policies that differ from Guildomatic. Guildomatic is not responsible for their privacy practices, nor does Guildomatic control how information may be provided through such third parties. 

#### Email updates and announcements

From time to time, users may receive announcements and updates with information related to services, products or special offers. You may opt-out of these emails at any time, but by doing so, you may not receive updates in regards to Guildomatic service changes or special events. 

#### Legal disclaimer

We have made reasonable efforts to ensure the security of any personally identifying information you have provided. Once this information is collected, it is only accessible internally to Guildomatic employees who need it to perform their jobs. 

These terms and conditions can be modified by us at any time. We will make sure links to the privacy policy are displayed prominently on our web site, and encourage you to review them periodically to ensure that you can raise any questions you might have to discuss with us further.
